regular meeting of the modern and special utility authority for today's day and time.
I don't too.
In the case of New York.
Hey, Benjamin.
Good.
You're just in time for the prayer.
By Mr. Steve Weitzel.
The Director of North Campus Minister.
Steve.
Thanks for that.
Thank you.
Young, a couple.
We've participated in our weekly Bible studies at the level of tonight.
I feel active from response to post and press conference.
We involved in all aspects that were simply set.
Yes.
First of all.
God, did you think for this night have we come?
In that city business?
We think for these who volunteer.
Just involved in sitting my on a awesome tax.
of the United States.
All of the lesson can I, as they meet in the business and records on all of us, we ask you
to continue to bless our city of Austin, Texas.
Thank you, Lord, for being subject to this.
Thank you.
Please join me in the pledge.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
Okay.
Adam 4 is public input on schedule personal appearances and when the audience was to address the authority
on the immediate agenda.
So there being now out of five is the consent agenda.
Staff that is recommending out of six and seven which are claims and minutes for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions, I'm going to hand-time most to approve.
Second.
Roll call please.
Four.
Five.
Lewis.
Aye.
Four.
Eight.
New business.
Anyone?
Nine.
Staff reports.
Correct.
They will portrait in the packet.
If available staff is present for questions.
No questions.
Trustee.
I'm 10.
Community announcements.
I'm 11 is adjourned.
I'll make a most to adjourn.
Do we have a second.
Roll call please.
Aye.
Work it.